University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  - Job 051014 NSO U College, 2005; UA206.001.263; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 148, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00033; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 121, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00034; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 086, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00035; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 058, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00036; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 044, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00037; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 029, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00038; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 003, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00039; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 076, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00040; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 056, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00041; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 036, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00042; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Parents' Weekend panel discussion about the University College (now Tisch College) in the Rabb room of the Lincoln Filene Center. Photo 004, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.263.00043; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 051014 SAR Deans, 2005; UA206.001.264; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 003, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00001; Arkin, Sarah
      Parents' Weekend. Introduction to the Deans of the Undergraduate Schools Linda Abriola, dean of the School of Engineering, presents: ÌÄåÕWater: Innovative Technology or Perpetual Stewardship?ÌÄåÒ Robert Sternberg, dean of the School of Arts and Sciences, presents: ÌÄåÕLeadership, Intelligence, and Stupidity.ÌÄåÒ In Braker Hall 001.
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 085, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00002; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 073, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00003; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 051, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00004; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 020, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00005; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 071, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00006; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 028, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00007; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 066, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00008; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 026, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00009; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 084, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00010; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 002, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00011; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 079, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00012; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 058, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00013; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 063, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00014; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 022, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00015; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 006, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00016; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 089, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00017; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 074, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00018; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 044, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00019; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 018, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00020; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 031, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00021; Arkin, Sarah
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 016, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.264.00022; Arkin, Sarah
  - Job 051014 SAR Emmanuel, 2005; UA206.001.265; Arkin, Sarah
  - Job 051014 SLE Author Talk, 2005; UA206.001.266; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 021, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00001; Leonard, Spencer
      Parents' Weekend. Catherine Clinton, author of 'Harriet Tubman: The Road to Freedom,' kicks off the Tisch Library's installation of the national touring exhibition 'Forever Free: Abraham Lincoln's Journey to Emancipation.' A question-and-answer session and book signing follows.Tisch Library, Hirsh Reading Room, 3:30-5 p.m.
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 008, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00002; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 003, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00003; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 007, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00004; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 051, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00005; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 036, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00006; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 032, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00007; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 011, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00008; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 055, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00009; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 035, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00010; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 017, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00011; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 002, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00012; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 043, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00013; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 030, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00014; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 012, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00015; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 005, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00016; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 057, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00017; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 034, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00018; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 015, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00019; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 006, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00020; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 001, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00021; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 009, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00022; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 052, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00023; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 033, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00024; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 013, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00025; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 054, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00026; Leonard, Spencer
    - Parents' Weekend. Photo 039, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.266.00027; Leonard, Spencer
  - Job 051014 SLE Forever Free, 2005; UA206.001.267; Leonard, Spencer
  - Job 051014 SLE Wellner Reception, 2005; UA206.001.268; Leonard, Spencer
  - Job 051014 ZTZ Dance, 2005; UA206.001.269; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 266, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00001; Tzanev, Zara
      Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre.
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 227, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00002; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 203, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00003; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 162, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00004; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 049, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00005; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 217, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00006; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 204, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00007; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 177, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00008; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 243, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00009; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 205, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00010; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 181, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00011; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 252, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00012; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 213, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00013; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 187, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00014; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 145, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00015; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 106, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00016; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 265, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00017; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 233, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00018; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 208, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00019; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 182, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00020; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 122, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00021; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 063, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00022; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 193, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00023; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 149, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00024; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 025, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00025; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 073, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00026; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 058, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00027; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 275, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00028; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 247, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00029; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 240, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00030; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 034, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00031; Tzanev, Zara
    - Parents' Weekend dance class in Jackson Gym and drama performance in the Balch Arena Theatre. Photo 029, 2005-10-14; UA206.001.269.00032; Tzanev, Zara
  - Job 051015 BLO Cheap Sox, 2005; UA206.001.270; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 081, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend.
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 058, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 042, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 027, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 039, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 012, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 085, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 074, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 056, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 077, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00010; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 062, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00011; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 026, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00012; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 061, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 037, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 007, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 063, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 043, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 022, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 065, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 045, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 041, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - Cheap Sox Alumni Reunion Show in Goddard Chapel for Homecoming/Parents' Weekend. Photo 023, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.270.00022; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 051015 BLO Engineering, 2005; UA206.001.271; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 049, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Brenner's students helped parents build bridge models designed for elementary schools.
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 029, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 035, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 017, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 015, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 010, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 068, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 040, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 069, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 047, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00010; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 025, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00011; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 067, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00012; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 052, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 031, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 062, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 032, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 022, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 016, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 019, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 014, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 005, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 001, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00022; Loeb, Brian
    - Parents' Weekend presentation on bridges by Civil and Environmental Engineering Professor Brian Brenner in Pearson 104. Photo 053, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.271.00023; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 051015 BVE Luncheon, 2005; UA206.001.272; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 062, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00001; Versoy, Bethany
      Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House.
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 060, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00002; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 005, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00003; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 016, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00004; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 043, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00005; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 031, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00006; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 051, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00007; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 010, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00008; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 040, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00009; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 021, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00010; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 061, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00011; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 027, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00012; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 024, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00013; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 015, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00014; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 070, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00015; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 058, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00016; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 055, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00017; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 038, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00018; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 022, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00019; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 017, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00020; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 013, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00021; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 002, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00022; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 046, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00023; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 037, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00024; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 030, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00025; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 025, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00026; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 019, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00027; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 008, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00028; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 069, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00029; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 064, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00030; Versoy, Bethany
    - Parents' Weekend luncheon at Gifford House. Photo 056, 2005-10-15; UA206.001.272.00031; Versoy, Bethany